各位乘客 飞机即将降落洛衫机
Ladies and gentlemen, we're about to begin our descent into Los Angeles.
大家刚才听到的是 起落架的声音
The sound you just heard is the landing gear locking into place.
洛衫机天气晴朗 温度是72
Los angeles weather is clear. The temperature is 72.
飞机行程如预计的一样 历时4小时18分钟
We expect to make our 4 hour and 18 minute flight on schedule.
很感谢大家乘坐本班机
We have enjoyed having you on board
请扶好栏杆并站在右边
Please hold handrail and stand to the right
如果想越过前面请走左边
if you wish to pass, please do so on the left.
请大家注意 停车的时间限制为3分钟
You attention, please. Parking in the area is limited to three minutes only.
请留意好自己的车
Please do not leave your car unattended.
喂 你怎么了？
Hey, what's the matter?
客人们都在楼下 班 等着见你呢
The guests are all downstairs, Ben, waiting to see you.
看 爸爸 你可以和他们说 我再过一会才下去吗？
Look, dad, could you explain that I have to be alone for a while?
他们都是我们的老朋友了 班
These are all our good friends, Ben.
很多人在你出世的时候 就认识你了
Most of them have known you since you were born.
怎么了 班？
What is it, Ben?
我只是...
I'm just...
担心？
worried?
嗯...
Well...
担心什么？
About what?
我想是我的将来吧
I guess about my future.
那又怎么了？
What about it?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想要...
I want it to be...
要什么？
To be what?
与众不同
Different.
有什么不妥吗？ 没有
Is anything wrong?  No.
我们就下去了 卡尔森一家也来了
We're just on our way downstairs. The Carlsons are here.
是吗？噢
They are? Well.
他们从塔桑那过来的
They came all the way from Tarzana.
我们一起去吧
let's get cracking.
有这么多好朋友在真好啊
It's a wonderful thing to have so many devoted friends.
噢奖学金得主出现了！
Hey, there's the award- winning scholar!
我们都为你感到骄傲 班 谢谢你 卡尔森太太
We're all very proud of you, Ben. Thank you, Mrs. Carlsons.
外面那辆红色开篷小车 是你的吗？
Is that the new car out there? That little red wop job?
那是班的毕业礼物
That's Ben's graduation present.
是啊 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
失陪了 我要去看看我的车子
Excuse me. I' d like to check something on the car for a minute.
他爸爸给他买的
His father bought him.
嘿 是你啊大明星
Hey, here's the track star.
你好吗?
How are you?
你在这里等吧
You wait right here.
班！
Ben!
我们感到很骄傲
We're all so proud of you.
骄傲...
Proud...
你接下来要做什么？
What are you going to do?
我要上楼一会儿
I was going to go upstairs for a minute.
噢 现在有点难说啊
Well, that's a little hard to say.
班
Ben.
过来一下 我有话和你说
Come here. I want to talk to you.
不好意思 祖安
Excuse us, Joanne.
恭喜你！
Congratulations!
我只是想和你说一句话
I just want to say one word to you.
就一句话
Just one word.
好的
Yes, sir.
你在听吗？是啊
Are you listening? Yes, I am.
塑胶业
Plastics.
塑胶业的前景一定很好
There's a great future in plastics.
考虑一下吧
Think about it.
你会考虑吗？ 我会的
Will you think about it? Yes, I will.
不好意思失陪了
Excuse me just a minute.
我拿到了班的大学记事本了
I've got ben's college yearbook.
我想把班的一些精彩的事情 读出来给大家听听
And I want to read you some of the wonderful things about Ben.
请安静！
Be quiet, please!
这里应该不是洗手间吧？
I guess this isn't the bathroom, is it?
洗手间在楼下
It's down the hall.
你好吗班？很好谢谢罗宾森太太
How are you, Benjamin? Fine, thank you, Mrs. Robinson.
洗手间就在楼下的尽头
The bathroom's down at the end of the hall.
我很希望... 这里有烟灰罐吗？
I' m awfully... Is there an ashtray in here?
没有
No.
噢我忘记你是不抽烟的了
Oh, I forgot you don't smoke.
为了女孩子吗？
Is it a girl?
什么女孩子？
Is what a girl?
使你沮丧的那个啊
Whatever it is that's upsetting you.
噢不我只是... 对一些事情感到烦恼
Oh, no, I' m just, uh... sort of disturbed about things.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
噢 班
Oh, Benjamin.
我希望你帮我个忙 什么？
I want to ask you something. What?
可以送我回家吗？ 什么？
Will you take me home? What?
我丈夫把车开走了 你能送我回去吗？
My husband took the car. Will you drive me home?
你会开车的吧？
You know how to work a foreign shift?
不会？ 不
You don't?   No
我们走吧
Let's go.
谢谢 好的
Thank you.  Right.
和我进去一下好吗？
Will you come in with me?
什么？
What?
为什么？
What for?
因为我觉得不安全
Because I don't feel safe.
但那里有灯光啊
But it's light in there.
请你了
Please.
你想喝什么？波旁酒？
What do you drink? Bourbon?
罗宾森太太 我很乐意送你回家
Mrs. Robinson, I drove you home, I was glad to do it.
你想喝什么？
What do you drink?
为什么呢？
Why not?
请等我丈夫回来之后 再离开
Please wait till my husband gets home.
他什么时候回来？
When is he coming back?
我不知道
I don't know.
喝酒吗？ 不
Drink?  No.
你总是那样害怕孤单吗？
Are you always this much afraid of being alone?
是的
Yes.
那你为什么不锁上门然后睡觉呢？
Well, why can't you just lock the doors and go to bed?
我经常失眠的
I'm very neurotic.
可以问你一个问题吗？
May I ask you a question?
你觉得我怎么样？
What do you think of me?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你出世的时候我就认识你了 你一定对我有一些想法的
You've known me nearly all your life. You must have formed some opinions of me.
我一直觉得你是一个很好的人
I always thought that you were a very nice person.
你以前知道我是个酒鬼吗？
Did you know I was an alcoholic?
什么？
What?
你知道吗？
Did you know that?
看来我应该走了
Look, I think I should be going.
坐下班
Sit down, Benjamin.
现在 我确信罗宾森先生很快就回来了...
Now, I' m sure Mr. Robinson will be here any minute...
不 什么？
No.  What?
我丈夫很晚才回来的
My husband will be back quite late.
他一出去就应该好几个小时
He should be gone for several hours.
噢天啊 什么？
Oh, my god.  Pardon?
噢不罗宾森太太不
Oh, no, Mrs. Robinson. No.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
什么？
What?
怎样的事情？
Like what?
你认为呢？我不知道啊
What do you think? Well, I don't know.
天啊
For god's sake,
罗宾森太太你把我带进屋里
Mrs. Robinson You got me into your house,
请我喝酒听那种音乐
you give me a drink, you put on music,
你开始和我谈论你的私生活
now you start opening up your personal life to me
还告诉我 你丈夫不会那么早回来
and telling me your husband won't be home for hours.
所以呢？
So?
罗宾森太太你想引诱我
Mrs. Robinson, you're trying to seduce me.
不是吗？
Aren't you?
不我没有想过
Well, no, I hadn't thought of it.
我受宠若惊呢
I feel very flattered.
可以原谅我刚才说的话吗？
Will you forgive me for what I just said?
没事
It's all right.
不是的 那是我说过的最难听的话
It's not all right. It 's the worst thing I ever said to anyone.
坐下吧
Sit down.
请原谅我我很喜欢你的
Please forgive me, because I like you.
我不应该那样看你 但我很烦恼
I don't think of you that way, but I' m mixed up.
没事的喝酒吧
It's all right. Finish your drink.
罗宾森太太 我那样说你真的很不该
Mrs. Robinson, it makes me sick that I said that to you.
很快就会忘记的喝酒吧
We'll forget it right now. Finish your drink.
我到底怎么了？
What is wrong with me?
你看过伊琳的肖像画吗？
Have you ever seen Elaine's portrait?
她的照片？
her portrait?
就在伊琳的房间里
It's here in Elaine's room.
伊琳是个很吸引人的女孩 是吗？
Elaine certainly is an attractive girl, isn't she?
我忘记了她的眼睛是棕色的
I don't remember her as having brown eyes.
班 什么？
Benjamin.  Yes?
你来这里一下好吗？
Will you come over here a minute?
那里？ 是的
Over there? Mm Hmm.
好的
Sure.
帮我把拉链拉下来好吗？
Will you unzip my dress?
我就要睡觉了
I think I' II go to bed.
噢那晚安了
Oh, well, good night.
不帮我了吗？
Won't you unzip my dress?
不了 罗宾森太太
I'd rather not, Mrs. Robinson.
如果你还以为我想引诱你...
If you still think I'm trying to seduce you...
班杰明 你非常了解我的
Benjamin, you've known me all your life.
我知道但是...  来吧 我够不着
I know that, but... Come on, it's hard for me to reach.
谢谢 好的
Thank you. Right.
你害怕些什么？
What are you so scared of?
我没有害怕罗宾森太太
I'm not scared, Mrs. Robinson.
那你为什么要跑？
Then why do you keep running away?
你就要睡觉了我不应该逗留
Because you're going to bed. I don't think I should be up here.
你没看过有人穿这样的衣服吗？
Haven't you seen anybody in a slip before?
如果罗宾森先生 进来了会怎样呢？
What if Mr. Robinson walked in right now?
如果那样？
What if he did?
那样就很有趣了不是吗？
It would look pretty funny, wouldn't it?
你不认为他相信我们吗？
Don't you think he'd trust us?
他当然相信
Of course, he does,
但是他也会想到别的 任何人都会
but he might get the wrong idea. Anyone might.
班杰明 我不是在引诱你
Benjamin, I am not trying to seduce you.
你想我引诱你吗？
Would you like me to seduce you?
什么？
What?
你不是想这样说的吗？
Is that what you're trying to tell me?
我要回家了
I'm going home now.
我为我刚才所说的道歉
I apologize for what I said.
希望你会忘记我马上就回去
I hope you can forget it, but I' m going home right now.
你走之前帮我把钱包 拿上来好吗？
Will you bring up my purse before you go?
我要走了很 抱歉
I have to go now. I'm sorry.
我不想穿衣服再下去 你帮我拿上来好吗？
I really don't want to put this on again. Won't you bring it up?
在哪里？ 在大厅的桌上
Where is it? On the table in the hall.
罗宾森太太？ 我在浴室
Mrs. Robinson?  I' m in the bathroom.
你的钱包在这里
here's the purse.
可以拿上来吗？
Could you bring it up?
你走到楼梯口 我递给你
Come to the railing, and I' II hand it up.
班 我已经很讨厌那种猜疑了
Benjamin, I' m getting pretty tired of all the suspicion.
我把它放在楼梯口
I'm putting it on the top step.
好了班别这样对我了好吗？
For god's sake, Benjamin, will you stop acting this way and bring me the purse?
我把它放在l门口
I'm putting it here by the door.
把它递进来好吗？ 恐怕不行了
Will you bring it in to me? I' d rather not.
好了把它放在伊琳房间里吧
All right. Put it in Elaine's room where we were.
好的
Right.
噢 天啊
Oh, god.
噢 让我出去
Oh, let me out.
别紧张  离开那门口
Don't be nervous.  Get away from that door.
让我先说 天啊
I want to say something first. Jesus christ.
噢 天啊  如果这次你不想和我睡觉
Oh, my christ.  Lf you won't sleep with me this time,
以后你随时可以找我
I want you to know you can call me up anytime,
你明白我意思吗？  让我出去
Do you understand what I' m saying?  Let me out.
班杰明 你明白吗？  明白 让我出去
Benjamin, do you understand? Yes, yes, let me out.
我觉得你很有吸引力
I find you very attractive.
这不是班的车子吗？是的
Is that Ben's car in front? Yes, sir.
我送罗宾森太太回来的
I drove Mrs. Robinson home.
她想我送她回来 所以我就来了
She wanted me to drive her home, so I drove her home.
噢 很感谢你这样做
well. I appreciate it.
她在楼上 她叫我在这里等你回来
She's upstairs. She wanted me to wait down here till you got home.
在这里做守卫吗？
Standing guard over the old castle, are you?
是的
Yes.
恭喜你
congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
有什么不妥吗？
Is anything wrong?
你好象在颤抖啊
You look a little shaken up.
噢 没什么 只是有点担心将来
Oh, no, I' m just a little worried about my future.
威士忌？
Scotch?
波旁酒
Bourbon.
班...
Ben...
你多大了？
How old are you now?
20 下周就21了
20. I'll be 21 next week.
那是黄金年华啊
That's a hell of a good age to be.
谢谢
Thank you.
很感谢你 先生
Thank you very much, sir.
我也希望回到那个年纪
I wish I was that age again.
因为 班...什么？
Because, ben...Sir?
时光一去不复返啊
You'll never be young again.
我知道
I know.
班 我可以和你说一些事吗？
Ben, can I say something to you?
什么？
What?
我们认识多久了？
how long have we known each other now?
你父亲和我做搭档有多久了？
How long have your dad and I been partners?
很长时间了
Quite a while.
我看着你长大的班 是的
I watched you grow up, Ben. Yes, sir.
我把你当成是我儿子一样的
I feel as though you were my own son.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以我希望你不会介意 我给你一些劝告
So I hope you won't mind my giving you a friendly piece of advice.
我洗耳恭听
I'd like to hear it.
班...
Ben...
我觉得...
I think...
我觉得你应该...轻松一点来对待现在的情况
I think you ought to be taking it...a little easier right now than you seem to be.
和女孩子约会等等
Have a good time with the girls and so forth.
不用起来
Don't get up.
我刚在说...
I was just telling...
你觉得那建议好吗？
You think that's sound advice?
很好
Yes, I do.
我要回去了
I've got to go.
这个暑假好好快活一下吧
You have yourself a few flings this summer.
我敢打赌你会很受女孩子欢迎
I bet you're quite a ladies' man.
噢 不 什么？
Oh, no. What?
你就是一个很有魅力的男人
You look to me like the kind of guy who has to fight them off.
是啊
Yes, he does.
噢 伊琳下周六就从伯克莱回来了
Oh... Elaine gets down from berkeley on saturday.
我会的
I will.
班
Benjamin.
班？ 什么事？
Ben? Yes.
谢谢你送我回家
Thank you for taking me home.
各位请注意了
Ladies and gentlemen, your attention, please.
喂看过来啊！
Hey, over there!
请你们注意
Your attention, please.
爸爸我们能谈一谈吗？
Could I speak to you for a second, dad?
听着 你们必须用热烈的掌声把这位小男孩请出来明白吗？
Listen, I' m going to ask for a big round of applause to bring this boy out here, all right?
我要补充一下
Let me amend that.
好了！开始吧！大家都在等
Yeah! Let's go! Our food's cold.
噢 我有几句话要说
Oh, I've got a few words to say.
你又来了
You always do.
看谁说话了
Look who's talking.
爸爸 我们能说一下吗？
Dad, can we just talk about this for a second?
我不能再拖延了 班 你最好出来吧
I can't hold them much longer, Ben. You better get out.
我想讨论一下
I'd like to discuss this.
这位年轻人将用奖学金继续深造
this young man is soon to continue his education as a frank halpingham award scholar,
好了让我们欢迎 班杰明.布莱迪！
Ok, let's hear it now for Benjamin Braddock!
来啊 班！
Come out, Benjy!
喂？
Hello?
我不知道为什么会这样
I don't quite know how to put this.
我在想那次晚会之后 发生的事...
I was thinking about that time after the party...
你在哪里？
Where are you?
你订了房间吗？
Did you get a room?
没有
No.
我知道现在很晚了 如果你...
Now, I know it's pretty late, and if you'd rather...
给我一个小时 什么？
Give me an hour. What?
我一个小时后到
I'll be there in an hour.
就在大舞厅
It's in the main ballroom.
在那里
Over there.
有什么可以帮你吗先生？
Can I help you, sir?
什么？噢我只是...
What? Oh, no, I' m just...
有什么事吗先生？
Are you here for an affair, sir?
什么？  参加辛格曼先生的派对？
What?  The singleman party, sir?
噢 对了 辛格曼先生的派对
Oh, yes. The singleman party.
在大舞厅里面 哦 谢谢
It 's in the main ballroom.  Ahh. Thank you.
你好 你好
Hello.  Hello.
你一定是服务员吧  不 我不是
You must be one of the porters.  No, I' m not.
这是我的先生辛格曼先生
that's my husband Mr. Singleman.
噢 不好意思  那是杰弗里
Oh, sorry.  That's Jeffrey.
其实我是来找我朋友的
actually, I'm just looking for a friend.
噢 我不明白了
Well, I don't understand.
我不是很明白啊
I don't get it.
很高兴你来 布迪夫先生
I've enjoyed meeting you, Mr. Braniff.
你好吗 班？  噢 你好
Hello Benjamin? -  Oh, hello.
可以坐吗？当然
May I sit down?   Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吗？ 很好谢谢
How are you?  Very well, thank you.
可以要一杯饮料吗？ 饮料？当然可以
May I have a drink?  A drink? Of course.
他看不到我 服务员
He didn't see me. Waiter.
我要一杯马天尼  好的夫人
I will have a martini.  Yes, ma'am.
你不必那么紧张的
You don't have to be so nervous.
紧张？
Nervous?
你订了房间吗？什么？
Did you get us a room? What?
你已经订了房间吗？
Have you gotten us a room yet?
不 还没有
I haven't, no.
你想那样做吗？
Do you want to?
或者我们就在这里聊天吧
Or we could just talk.
你想我去开房间吗？
You want me to get it?
不 不 我去吧
No, no, I' II get it.
你想现在就去吗？现在？
Do you want to get it now? Now?
是的
Yes.
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
不好意思
Excuse me.
什么事先生？
Yes, sir?
我要开一个房间
I'd like a room
单人房还是双人房？
A single room or a double room?
请在这里登记
Sign the register, please.
有什么出错了吗？没什么
Anything wrong, sir? nothing.
你有带行李吗 格莱斯登先生？
Do you have any luggage, Mr. Gladstone?
行李？有啊
Luggage? Yes,I do.
在哪里？什么？
Where is it? What?
行李在哪里？
Where is your luggage?
在外面的车上
It's out there in the car.
那我叫人帮你拿进来
I'll have a porter bring it in.
噢 不
Oh, no.
我的意思是...
I mean...
我自己拿就可以了
I can get it myself.
好的
Of course.
那我叫人带你去房间吧
I'll have a porter show you the room.
我可以自己处理
I can handle it myself.
谢谢
Thank you.
罗宾森太太吗？ 什么事？
Mrs. Robinson?  Yes?
找你的
For you.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂 罗宾森太太？
Hello.   Mrs. Robinson?
我是班
It 's Benjamin.
班杰明.布莱迪
Benjamin Braddock.
班杰明 你在哪里？
Benjamin, where are you?
看到我了吗？看到了
Can you see me?  Yes, I can.
我要了一个单人房  很好
I got a single room.   That's fine.
那个接待员好象开始怀疑我了
The desk clerk seemed to be a little bit suspicious.
你想先上去？  是的我想那样好些
Do you want to go up first?  Yes, I think that would be good.
我5分钟之后上去
I'll be up in 5 minutes.
那 再见 班
Good- bye, then.  Benjamin.
什么？
Yes?
你是不是有些事情要告诉我呢？
Isn't there something you want to tell me?
告诉你？ 是的
Tell you?   Yes.
号码 什么？
The number.  What?
房间号码啊 班 我想你应该告诉我的
The room number, Benjamin. I think you ought to tell me that.
你说的对
You're absolutely right.
谢谢 不客气
Thank you. You're welcome.
那么...
Well...
迟点见罗宾森太太
I'll see you later, Mrs. Robinson.
请登记
Check, please.
我拿到了 嗯？
I got it.   Hmm?
我说我拿到了 先生？
I say I got it.  Sir?
牙刷 我拿了 好了
The toothbrush. I got it, all right.
很好先生 是的
Very good, sir. Yes.
晚安 晚安先生
good night.  Good night, sir.
你好 班
Hello, Benjamin.
你好 罗宾森太太
Hello, Mrs. Robinson.
班...
Benjamin...
好的
Sure.
我不知道你想我做什么
I don't know what you want me to do.
为什么不看着呢？ 噢 是的 谢谢
Why don't you watch? Oh, sure. Thank you.
帮我拿个衣架来好吗？  什么？
Will you bring me a hanger?   What?
衣架 噢 好的
A hanger. Oh, yes.
木的？
Wood?
什么？
What?
要木的还是钢的？两种都有
Wood or wire? They have both.
随便哪种都可以 好的
Either one would be fine. Ok.
谢谢
Thank you.
帮我一下好吗？
Would you help me with this, please?
好
Certainly.
谢谢 不客气
Thank you. You're welcome.
班 在黑暗里你会好过些 对吗？
Benjamin, would this be easier for you in the dark?
罗宾森太太 我不能这样做
Mrs. Robinson, I can't do this.
你什么？ 这样太不应该了
You what?  This is all terribly wrong.
我觉得你是我父母的朋友中最吸引人的一个了
I think you're the most attractive of all my parents' friends.
他们会说什么？ 我不知道罗宾森太太
What would they say? I have no idea, Mrs. Robinson,
他们给了我很好的生活
They made a good life for me,
你害怕我吗？
Are you afraid of me?
噢 不是 你误解了...
Oh, no, you're missing the point...
我们可以一起做些别的事情
we could do something else together.
罗宾森太太 我们去看电影好吗？
Mrs. Robinson, would you like to go to a movie?
可以问你一个私人问题吗？
Can I ask you a personal question?
这是你的第一次吗？
Is this your first time?
是什么？是的对吧？
Is this what?  It is, isn't it?
这是你的第一次
It is your first time.
这真的很好笑罗宾森太太
That's a laugh, Mrs. Robinson.
你可以承认的对吗？
You can admit that, can't you?
没什么要觉得羞愧的
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
等一等 你的第一次...
Wait a minute. your first time...
谁说这是我的第一次？
Who said it was my first time?
是因为你很不自然
Just because you happen to be inadequate.
很不自然？
Inadequate?
我应该... 别动！
I better...Don't move!
班 你在做什么？
Ben, what are you doing?
我只是在池里漂浮
I' m just drifting here in the pool
为什么？
Why?
这样漂浮很舒服啊
it's very comfortable just to drift here.
你想过研究所的事情吗？
Have you thought about graduate school?
没有
No.
那些努力的意义是什么？
What was the point of all that hard work?
你难到我了
You got me.
听我说班...
listen, Ben...
罗宾森夫妇来了
Robinsons are here.
你好啊班 这些日子在做什么啊？
Hi, Ben. What are you doing with yourself these days?
噢 没做什么
Oh, not too much.
放松一下
Taking it easy.
那是我觉得应该做的 没什么不妥
That's what I' d do if I could. Nothing wrong with that.
伊琳很快就要回来了
Elaine's coming back soon.
这次你去约她吧
I want you to call her up this time.
我会的
I will.
我想你们一定很适合对方的
Because I just think you two would hit it off real well together.
向罗宾森太太问好啊 班
Say hello to Mrs. Robinson, Benjamin.
你好 罗宾森太太
Hello, Mrs. Robinson.
你好 班
Hello, Benjamin.
可以和你说几句吗？ 当然可以
Can I talk to you for a minute?   Sure.
班...
Ben...
亲爱的 我想问你一些事情但...
Darling, I' m going to ask you something, but you...
如果你不想的话 可以不用回答我的
You don't have to tell me if you don't want to.
什么？
What?
我想问你晚上 出去做什么
I' m going to ask you what you do when you go off at night.
出去外面？
When I go off?
你不想的话可以不用回答我
You don't have to tell me if you don't want to.
不 我会回答你的
No, I do. I want to tell you.
我只是驾车到处逛
I drive around.
没其他了？没有了
What else?  Nothing else.
你不会从半夜一直开车到处逛到下一天中午的 班
You don't drive around from midnight until noon the next day, Benjamin.
噢 不会
Oh, no.
那你做什么？
Well, then, what do you do?
和某人约会？
You meet someone?
约会？
Meet someone?
我没有和别人约会 妈妈 但你为什么说这些？
I don't meet anyone, mother, but why do you say that?
班杰明 我不想干扰你的私事
Benjamin, I don't want to pry into your affairs,
但我觉得你说的话很不诚实
but I would rather you didn't say anything at all than be dishonest.
等等！
Wait a minute!
等一等好吗？
Will you wait a minute, please?
罗宾森太太 这次我们先互相说几句再开始好吗？
Mrs. Robinson, do you think we could say a few words to each other first this time?
我想我们之间没什么好说的
I don't think we have much to say to each other.
你厌倦了吗？
Are you tired of it?
不 我不是
I'm not, no.
你到底想说什么？
What do you want to talk about?
你想告诉我 你在大学时的一些经历吗？
Do you want to tell me about some of your college experiences?
噢 天啊
Oh, my god.
想别的话题吧
Think of another topic.
艺术怎么样？
How about art?
艺术 这是个很好的话题
Art. That's a good subject.
你开头吧
You start it off.
你开头吧 我一点也不懂
You start it off. I don't know anything about it.
那你想知道些什么？
Well, what do you want to know about it?
你更喜欢现代艺术 还是古典艺术？
Are you interested more in modern art or in classical art?
两个都不
Neither.
你对艺术没有兴趣？ 没有
You're not interested in art?   No.
那你为什么想说艺术？
Then why do you want to talk about it?
我不想的
I don't.
告诉我你今天做了些什么吧
Tell me what you did today.
我起床
I got up.
帮我丈夫做早餐 对了
I fixed breakfast for my husband.  There.
我们可以说一下你丈夫的事情
There's something we could have a conversation about your husband.
噢 他
Oh. Him.
我不知道你是怎么应付过来的
I don't know anything about how you work this.
你晚上离开屋子的时候和他说什么的？
What do you say to him when you leave the house at night?
没什么 他睡着了
Nothing. He's asleep.
每次都是？
Always?
你回来的时候不会吵醒他？
Doesn't he wake up when you come home?
我们有不同的卧室
We have separate bedrooms.
噢 是这样
Oh, I see.
我不是想多管闲事 但你们似乎不是一起睡觉的
I don't like to seem like I' m prying, but I guess you don't sleep together.
这样有多久了？
How long has this been going on?
好了别说这个了 等一等
For god's sake, let's drop this.   Wait a minute.
你为什么嫁给他？
Why did you marry him?
看你能不能猜到了
See if you can guess.
认真想想吧 班杰明
Think real hard, Benjamin.
不要告诉伊琳
Don't tell Elaine.
噢 不 你嫁给他是因为你怀孕了
Oh, no. You had to marry him because you got pregnant.
你很震惊吗？
Are you shocked?
我从来没想到罗宾森先生 和你是那种...
I never thought of you and Mr. Robinson as the kind of people who...
好了 我们睡觉吧
All right now, let's get to bed.
等等
Wait a minute.
那是怎样发生的？
So how did it happen?
什么？你和罗宾森先生
What? You and Mr. Robinson.
他那时是读法律的吗？ 是的
Was he a law student at the time?  Mm- hmm.
你那时也是学生吗？是的
And you were a student also?  Mm- hmm.
在大学？
At college?
是的
Yes.
你主修什么？
What was your major?
班杰明 为什么你要问这些问题？
Benjamin, why are you asking me all these questions?
因为我想知道啊 罗宾森太太
Because I' m interested, Mrs. Robinson.
你读大学时主修什么？
What was your major subject at college?
艺术 艺术？
Art.   Art?
我还以为你...
But I thought you...
那 我看这些年来 你已经对它失去兴趣了吧
I guess you kind of lost interest in it over the years, then.
应该是吧
Kind of.
那是怎样发生的？
Well, how did it happen?
什么？ 你和罗宾森先生
What? You and Mr. Robinson.
你认为呢？
How do you think?
你带他来这个房间的吗？
Did you take you up to his room with him?
你们去酒店的吗？
Did you go to a hotel?
噢 班 那有什么重要的吗？
Oh, Benjamin, what does it possibly matter?
我很好奇
I'm curious.
我们上了他的车 噢不
We'd go to his car.   Oh, no.
你们在车上做的？
In the car you did it?
我想我们不是第一个这样的
I don't think we were the first.
那是什么车？
What kind of car was it?
什么？
What?
还记得那是什么车吗？
Do you remember the make of the car?
噢天啊 我真的想知道
Oh, my god.  Really, I want to know.
是福特 本杰明
It was a ford, Benjamin.
福特
A ford.
福特 该死的 很不错啊
A ford. God damn it, that's great.
够了
That's enough.
不要说伊琳
Don't talk about Elaine.
不要说伊琳？
Don't talk about Elaine?
是的
No.
为什么不？
Why not?
我想你来告诉我
I wish you'd tell me.
没什么好说的
There's nothing to tell.
看来我要约伊琳出来问清楚
I guess I' II have to ask her out on a date and find out what the big deal is.
班杰明 你不许和她约会
Benjamin, don't you ever take that girl out.
你明白了吗？
Do you understand that?
我无意约她出来的
I have no intention of taking her out.
好
Good.
我只是开个玩笑
I was just kidding around.
好
Good.
不行
No.
我甚至配不上说起她 对吗？
I'm not good enough to even talk about her, am I?
不要再说了 不说不行
Let's drop it.   We're not dropping it.
我配得上你 但配不起和你女儿有联系
I'm good enough for you, but I' m not good enough to associate with your daughter.
就是这样 是吗？班杰明
That's it, isn't it? Benjamin.
是吗？
Isn't it?
是的
Yes.
你以为我为这种事骄傲吗？  我不想知道
Do you think I' m proud of this?  I wouldn't know.
我明白了
I see.
如果你以为我是因为寂寞 才来找你就大错特错了
If you think I come here for any reason besides pure boredom than you're all wrong.
那是因为罗宾森太太
'Cause, Mrs. Robinson,
这是我做过的 最令自己恶心的事情
this is the sickest, most perverted thing that ever happened to me.
你做到了你想做的事 但我却在受罪
You do what you want, but I' m getting the hell out.
是吗？
Are you?
别开始 什么？
don't start this.   What?
别开始扮作伤心
Don't start acting hurt.
你不希望我会有一点伤心吗？
Don't you expect me to be a little hurt?
我有那样说吗？
Did I say that?
两分钟前你说 我配不上你女儿
2 minutes ago you told me I wasn't good enough for your daughter.
我无意的
I didn't mean it.
我认为你们是合不来的
I don't think you'd be right for each other.
但我不认为你比不上她
I'd never say you aren't as good a person as she is.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
刚才我有点不知所措
I was kind of upset there.
我为我说的话道歉
I'm sorry I said those things.
没关系
It's all right.
我知道自己为什么如此让你讨厌
I think I can understand why I' m disgusting to you.
噢 不
Oh, no.
我喜欢你 不然我不会来这里
I like you. I wouldn't keep coming here if I didn't like you.
但那不是令你很难受的吗？
But if it's sickening for you?
不是
It's not.
你不必这样说
You don't have to say that.
那我可以留下来吗？
May I stay, then?
谢谢 不必谢我
Thank you. Well, don't.
我想你作出承诺
I want you to promise me that.
我不会和她约会的
It never occurred to me to take her out.
那就保证你不会吧！
Then give me your word you won't!
真有点荒唐
This is absurd.
答应我 班杰明
Promise me, Benjamin.
好的 我保证
All right, I promise.
谢谢
Thank you.
不要再说了
Let's not talk at all.
伊琳很快就回来了
Elaine's back home soon.
我想应该是你 和她约会的好时机了
I think it might be a nice gesture if you asked her out.
伊琳和我是合不来的
Elaine Robinson and I do not get along.
这和那没有关系
That has nothing to do with it.
我应该告诉罗宾森先生...
I' II just have to tell Mr. Robinson...
你好
Hello.
进来吧 班
Ben, come on in.
我想那年轻小姐还没准备好呢
I'm afraid the young lady isn't quite ready yet.
还是喝威士忌吗？  波旁酒
Scotch still your drink?  Bourbon.
班杰明 我想我已经讲得很清楚的了
Benjamin, I thought I made myself perfectly clear about this.
我想我应付不了那样
I' m afraid I couldn't handle that.
我不会再约你的宝贝女儿出去的
I have no intention of ever taking your precious daughter out again,
你好
Hello.
你现在住在家里 对吗？
You're living at home now, is that right?
是的
Yes.
没有
No.
你想读研究生吗？
Are you going to graduate school?
不
No.
你总是这样驾车的吗？
Do you always drive like this?
是的
Yes.
请坐
Sit down.
你为什么不看表演？
Why don't you watch the show?
班杰明 你是不是讨厌我？
Benjamin, do you dislike me for some reason?
我不知道
I don't know.
你觉得怎样？
How do you like that?
你可以那样做吗？
Could you do it?
去啊宝贝！
Go, baby, go!
停！ 喂！
Stop!  Hey!
伊琳 对不起
Elaine, I' m sorry.
伊琳
Elaine.
送我回家好吗？
Would you take me home now?
伊琳
Elaine.
车在哪里？
Where's the car?
我想和你说一些话
I just want to tell you something.
我要回家
I want to go home.
什么？
What?
他们逼我这样做的
They forced me into it.
很感谢你告诉我
That's very nice of you to tell me.
我不是那样的人
I'm not like this.
请你不要再哭了好吗？
could you just stop crying, please?
我忍不住
No, I couldn't.
你试一下好吗？  不行啊
could you try?  No.
自从我毕业以后...
since I' ve graduated...
你明白我的意思吗？
You know what I mean?
明白
Yes, I do.
我觉得就像在玩一种游戏，但规则对我来说毫无意义
It's like I was playing some kind of game,but the rules don't make any sense to me.
它们都是某些人错误地制造出来的
They're being made up by all the wrong people.
不
No.
喂！
Say!
你能把音量调小一点吗？
Could I request that you turn that down?
你想进屋里吗？
Would you like to come in?
我请你喝杯咖啡
I could make you some coffee.
不了 我不想打扰其他人
No. I wouldn't want to wake anyone up.
不会的
We won't.
我们进去吧
Let's go inside.
等等
Wait a minute.
怎么了？
Is anything wrong?
没什么 我只是在想...
No. I was just thinking.
现在还早着呢
It's still early.
好啊
All right.
我们去哪里？
Where are we going?
怎么了？
What is the matter?
没什么 我不知道那里有没有酒吧
Nothing. I' m just wondering if they have a bar or not.
晚安
Good evening.
你好 你好先生
Hello. How are you, sir?
晚上好 格莱斯登先生
Good evening, Mr. Gladstone.
你好
Hello.
格莱斯登先生 晚上好啊
Mr. Gladstone. How are you this evening?
班杰明？
Benjamin?
我们走吧 伊琳 去其他地方
Let's get out of here, Elaine. Let's go somewhere else.
他们认识你吗？  当然不认识了
Do they know you?  Of course not.
晚上好 先生  伊琳我们走吧
Good evening, sir.  Elaine, we're leaving.
格莱斯登先生 你好吗？
Mr. Gladstone, how are you?
班杰明 到底怎么了？
Benjamin, what's happening?
他们把我当成 是什么格莱斯登先生了
They must think I look like this guy Gladstone.
你好 布迪夫先生
Hello, Mr. Braniff.
伊琳 我很喜欢你
Elaine, I like you so much.
你相信我吗？
Do you believe that?
是吗？ 是的
Do you?   Yes.
你是第一个...
You're the first...
我的一生就那么浪费了
My whole life is such a waste.
徒劳无功
It's just nothing.
不好意思 我现在送你回家
I'm sorry. I'll take you home now.
对不起
I'm sorry.
已经发生了
It just happened.
它就像其他事情那样发生了
It's just this thing that happened along with everything else.
你明白吗？
Can you understand that?
她结了婚？
Was she married or something?
是的
Yes.
有家庭？
With a family?
是的 她有丈夫和孩子
Yes. She had a husband and a son.
他们发现了吗？ 没有
Did they ever find out?   No.
说完了吗？
And it's all over now?
是的
Yes.
我很开心
I'm glad.
我们明天去做别的好吗？
Can we do something tomorrow?
好啊
All right.
好
Ok.
你真的想去吗？是的
You sure you really want to?  Yes.
我希望你是真的愿意
Because I wouldn't want you to do it unless you really wanted to.
我愿意
I do.
真的？
You do?
班杰明 我真的愿意 嘘！
Benjamin, I really do.   Shh!
一直开下去
Drive down the block.
罗宾森太太
Mrs. Robinson,
按我说的做
Do exactly as I say.
听清楚了 班杰明
Listen to me very carefully, Benjamin.
你以后不要再和伊琳见面
You are not to see Elaine again ever.
那是我的命令
Those are my orders.
我可以把事情搞砸的
I can make things quite unpleasant.
怎样？
How?
为了让伊琳远离你 我会把所有的事都告诉她
In order to keep Elaine away from you, I' m prepared to tell her everything.
我不敢相信你
I don't believe you.
那你最好开始相信我了
Then you'd better start believing me.
该死的
God damn it.
伊琳！伊琳！
Elaine! Elaine!
班杰明 我上来了！
Benjamin.  I' m coming up!
我还没穿衣服啊
I'm not dressed yet.
班杰明 我说我还没穿衣服啊
Benjamin, I said I wasn't dressed.
班杰明
Benjamin.
班杰明 你在做什么？ 伊琳...
Benjamin, what are you doing?   Elaine...
我要告诉你一些事  什么事？
I have to tell you something.   What is it?
那个女人... 女人？
That woman...  Woman?
你说那个？ 是的
You mean that one?   Yes.
班杰明 你能告诉我这是什么吗？
Benjamin, would you just tell me what this is about?
噢 不 伊琳
Oh, no.  Elaine.
天啊 求你
Oh, my god.  Please.
出去 不要哭
Get out of here.  Don't cry.
出去！出去！
Get out! Get out!
出去！
Get out!
再见 班杰明
Goodbye, Benjamin.
再说一次？
Say that again?
我要娶伊琳
I'm going to marry Elaine.
好啊 好啊！ 怎么了？
Well, well!   What's happening?
班说他和伊琳就要结婚了
Ben says that he and Elaine are getting married.
噢 班 太好了！
Oh, Ben, It 's so exciting!
我们要给罗宾森夫妇打个电话
We've got to call the Robinsons.
我们要好好庆祝一下
We've got something to celebrate.
噢 他们还不知道？
Oh, they don't know?
你什么时候决定的？
When did you decide all this?
等等 你今天早上和伊琳说的吗？
Wait a minute. You talked to Elaine this morning?
不 她还不知道
No. She doesn't know about it.
你是说她还不知道 你要去伯克莱？
You mean she doesn't know that you're coming up to berkeley?
不 其实她还不知道我们要结婚的事
No. Actually, she doesn't know about us getting married yet.
那是我作出的决定
It's a decision I' ve made.
那你怎么认为她想嫁给你？
Well, what makes you think she wants to marry you?
老实说她不喜欢我的
To be perfectly honest, she doesn't like me.
你是学生？ 不算是
You a student?  Not exactly.
那你是什么人？
What are you then?
我只是路过的旅客
I'm just sort of traveling through.
我只是来旅游
I'm just visiting.
我总是很想来这里的
I' ve always wanted to see berkeley.
你不是那种夜猫子吧？  什么？
You're not one of those agitators?  What?
我将忍受不了那样
I won't stand for that.
不好意思
Pardon me.
很巧啊对吧？
how about this for a coincidence?
我想知道你要去哪里？
I was wondering where you were headed.
我约了人
I'm meeting someone.
在哪里？
Where?
你约了那人在哪里见面？
Where are you meeting this person?
在动物园
At the zoo.
动物园
The zoo.
我也没有
I haven't, either.
我可以和你一起去那里的
I might just ride out there with you.
就是在那边那个吗？  不是
Is that him over there?  No.
他说好在哪里等的？
Where did he say he was going to meet you?
班杰明 我想知道你为什么要来这里
Benjamin, I would like to know what you're doing here.
我来这里听课啊
I' ve been getting into some classes.
但你没有注册的
But you're not enrolled.
真的不可思议
Really incredible.
他来了 什么？
Here he comes.   What?
我的直觉告诉我就是他了
I got a real feeling that this is the fella.
伊琳！
Elaine!
他很健壮哦
He certainly is a good walker.
我迟到了吗？不好意思
Am I late? I' m sorry.
这是班杰明.布莱迪 卡尔.史密斯
This is Benjamin Braddock. Carl smith.
班杰明和我一起坐车来的
Benjamin rode here with me on the bus.
很高兴见到你 班
Glad to meet you, Ben.
真的很高兴
Swell seeing you.
谁？
Who is it?
我只问你一个问题 然后我就走
I want to ask you a question, and then I' m going.
进来吧 不了
Come in.   No.
我想知道你为什么来这里
I want to know why you're here in berkeley.
因为...
Because...
是因为我在这里吗？
Is it because I' m here?
你认为呢？ 我认为是的
What do you think?   I think it is.
我说我觉得是 那就是了
I said I think it is.  All right, then. Yes.
我要你离开这里  我爱你
I want you to leave. I love you.
你怎么可以这样做？
How could you do that?
你怎么可以污辱我的母亲？
How could you possibly rape my mother?
什么？我不明白...
What? I don't understand...
她说了什么？告诉我
What did she say? Tell me.
为什么？ 因为那不是真的
Why? Because it isn't true.
告诉我
Tell me.
她说那时她正在酒店 和朋友喝酒
She said that she was having a drink at the hotel with a friend,
噢 然后呢？
Oh, then what?
然后你把她带上楼把她污辱了
Then you took her upstairs, and you raped her.
噢 不 事情不是那样的
Oh, no. That's not what happened.
我送你母亲回家...
I drove your mother home...
我们去你房间看你的肖像画...  不！
We went upstairs to see your portrait...   No!
她开始脱衣服
She started taking her clothes off
噢 不要说！
Oh, shut!
只是我的一个客人 现在没事了
It was just a visitor, but it's all right now.
你对她做了些什么？
What did you do to her?
她很压抑 叫了一声 但现在好了
She's upset, and she screamed, but it's ok now.
要叫警察来吗？什么？
Shall I get the cops?  What?
我去报警 喂 等一等
I' II get the cops.  Hey, wait a minute.
她就在这里喝着水
Here she is, having some water.
没必要叫警察来
There's no need for the cops or anything.
去吧
Go ahead.
我不想再发生这种事
We won't have any more of this agitation.
我要你搬走
I want you out of here.
为什么？因为我不喜欢你
What for? Because I don't like you.
伊琳 我现在不想说什么
Elaine, right now I don't feel like talking much.
你现在有什么打算？
What are you going to do now?
我不知道
I don't know.
你会回家吗？ 不
Are you going home?  No.
那你要去哪里？
where are you going?
伊琳 你不要再问了
Elaine, you're going to have to stop asking me that.
我不明白
I don't understand.
在你有明确的方向之前...我不想你去任何地方
I don't want you to go anywhere... Until you have a definite plan.
再见
Goodbye.
怎么了？
What's happening?
班杰明？ 什么？
Benjamin?   What?
亲我一下好吗？
Will you kiss me?
你愿意嫁给我吗？
Will you marry me?
你不想？ 我不知道
You won't?   I don't know.
是吗？
Is that so?
你可能会嫁给我？ 是的
You might marry me?  Yes.
什么时候？
When?
我不知道
I don't know.
明天回答我好吗？ 我不想逼你太紧
How about tomorrow? I don't mean to be pushy.
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what's happening.
你很迷惑吗？
You mean you're confused?
我们就要结婚了
We're getting married.
我要走了
I have to go now.
伊琳？
Elaine?
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious about this?
我会考虑清楚的
I'll think about it.
太好了
Good god.
我们明天可以去体检了
We can go get our blood tests tomorrow.
明天？ 今天下午也行
Tomorrow? Or this afternoon.
今天很好啊
It's a good day for it.
班杰明 我还没决定要嫁给你呢
Benjamin, I haven't even said I' II marry you yet.
要我们的出生证明的
We'll need our birth certificates.
我的刚好带在身上 你的呢？
I happen to have mine with me. Where's yours?
我就是觉得不太可行 为什么？
I just don't think it would work.   Why wouldn't it?
为什么？ 我就觉得不会
Why wouldn't it? I just don't think it would.
我们明天去体检好吗？
Can we get our blood tests tomorrow morning?
如果你那么想和我结婚 为什么不直接把我掳走呢？
Why don't you just drag me off if you want to marry me so much?
为什么不直接把你掳走？
Why don't I just drag you off?
好 体检之后我会做的
All right. I will, right after we get the blood tests.
我要先见卡尔
I have to see Carl first.
卡尔是谁？
Carl who?
在动物园的那个？ 是的
that guy at the zoo?   Yes.
他是怎么做的？
How did he do it?
没有
No.
他说了什么？我很好奇
What did he say? I'm curious.
嘘
Shh.
他说我和他会组织一个 好家庭的
He said he thought we'd make a pretty good family.
噢 他这样说了？ 嘘！
Oh, he said that?  Shh!
他在哪里做的？
Where did he do it?
我想知道在哪里发生的
I'd like to know where it happened.
晚安
Good night.
我们明天可以结婚吗？
Are we getting married tomorrow?
不
No.
后天呢？
The day after tomorrow?
你想解释一下 为什么你要那样做吗？
do you want to try and tell me why you did it?
罗宾森先生
Mr. Robinson.
你有什么特别憎恨我的吗？
Do you have a special grudge against me?
没有
No.
和你没有关系的 先生
It was nothing to do with you, sir.
班 和我绝对是有关系的
Ben, it was quite a bit to do with me.
班 我们是受过教育的人
Ben, I think we're civilized human beings.
你认为有必要这样互相威胁吗？
Do you think it's necessary to threaten each other?
我不是在威胁你
I'm not threatening you.
我想说我对你没有任何的成见
I'm trying to tell you I have no personal feelings about you.
你一点也不尊重我
You don't respect me terribly much.
不是的 什么？
No.   What?
不是  不要对我大喊 班
No.   Don't shout at me, Ben.
我没你那么年轻 但我的听觉还是很好的
I may not be as young as you, but I still have pretty good hearing.
罗宾森先生...  先等我说完
Mr. Robinson...   Have the decency to wait until I finish.
我想你应该明白你那样做的后果 会是怎样的
I do think you should know the consequences of what you've done.
我想你知道我和我妻子 很快就要离婚的
I do think you should know that my wife and I are getting a divorce soon.
为什么？
why?
听我说
Listen to me.
罗宾森太太和我之间的事...
What happened between Mrs. Robinson and me was nothing...
那并不代表什么
It didn't mean anything.
你误解了 我想是了
You miss the point.  I guess I do.
我喜欢的是你女儿 不是你太太
I don't love your wife. I love your daughter.
好了 现在听我说
All right. Now listen to this.
我不知道我是否可以起诉 但我想是可以的
I don't know whether I can prosecute, but I think I can.
我见过伊琳了 我可以肯定你不会得到她
I've seen Elaine, and I' ve made damn sure you can't get to her.
别碰我 班！
Stay away from me, Ben!
我不想和你浪费时间
I don't want to mince words with you.
你听清楚了吗？
Is that perfectly clear to you?
我说完了 班 别怪我不和你握手
that's all, Ben. You'll pardon me if I don't shake hands with you.
我觉得你很无耻
I think you are filth.
你很下流！
I think you are scum!
你是个废物！
You are a degenerate!
你好
Hi.
我要你马上离开这里
I want you out of here.
求你给我打个电话好吗？
For god's sake, will you let me use that phone?
我现在就去报警
I'm going to call the police now.
能让我先用电话吗？
Could I make one phone call first?
快滚！
Get out of here!
伊琳.罗宾森已经离开了学校
Elaine Robinson has left school
她的室友有个便条要给你
Her roommate's coming down with a note for you.
亲爱的班杰明 请你原谅我
Dear Benjamin, please forgive me,
因为我知道我这样做是为你好
because I know what I' m doing is the best thing for you.
我爱你 但这是没用的
I love you, but it would never work out.
伊琳？
Elaine?
你好啊 班杰明
Hello, Benjamin.
她在哪里？
Where is she?
你们在甘维街附近有巡警吗？
Do you have a patrol car in the vicinity of 1200 glenview road?
好 这里发生盗窃案
Good. We have a burglar here.
等等 我要问他 你带了武器吗？
Just a second. I' II ask him. Are you armed?
不 我想他没有
No, I don't believe he is.
谢谢
Thank you.
你对她做了什么？
What have you done to her?
我想事情都在我们控制之内了 班杰明
I think we have everything quite under control now, Benjamin.
你想在走之前喝一杯吗？
Would you like a quick drink before you go?
很抱歉没有邀请你去参加婚礼 班杰明
Sorry we won't be able to invite you to the wedding Benjamin,
我想你没时间喝酒了
I don't think you'll have time for that drink.
我会找到她的
I' II find her.  I don't think so.
知道卡尔现在在哪里吗？
Do any of you fellas know where carl smith is?
他昨晚深夜就离开了 说是去结婚
He took off in the middle of the night to get married.
走得比子弹还要快
Probably one step ahead of the shotgun.
我要去那里的
I'm supposed to be there.
卡特！
Carter!
圣芭芭拉！
Santa barbara!
我应该去参加的
I'm supposed to be there.
在圣芭芭拉哪里？
Where in santa barbara?
你要去参加婚礼吗？  是啊
you going to the wedding?   Yeah.
叫他给我留一份
tell him to save a piece for me.
我可以用一下你的电话吗？  好的
Can I use your phone?   Yeah.
喂 是谁？
Hello, who is this?
这里是史密斯医生的接待处
This is Dr. Smith's answering service.
我要知道他在哪里
I have to know where he is.
他去参加他儿子的婚礼 现在婚礼结束了
the doctor is at his son's wedding, but it's over by now.
谢谢你
Thank you.
亚兰街 怎么去？
Allan street, where is it?
噢 天啊
Oh, Jesus god.
伊琳！
Elaine!
那人是谁？
Who is that guy?
伊琳！
Elaine!
一定要阻止他！
We've got to stop him!
伊琳！
Elaine!
班！
Ben!
你这个疯子！
You crazy punk!
我要杀了你
I'll kill you.
伊琳！太迟了！
Elaine! It 's too late!
走开！ 该死的！
Move!  Damn you!